{
  "title": "New York DMV Driver (D) Practice Test",
  "ref": "https://dmv.ny.gov/driver-license/drivers-manual-practice-tests",
  "test": [
    {
      "id": "C4Q1",
      "answer": "B",
      "question": "You may cross a single solid white line in the highway:",
      "A": "A. Whenever you want to",
      "B": "B. If traffic conditions require",
      "C": "C. Only to turn into a driveway",
      "D": "D. Only to make a u-turn"
    },
    {
      "id": "C4Q2",
      "answer": "D",
      "question": "As you near an intersection, the traffic light changes from green to yellow.  Your best action would be to:",
      "A": "A. Speed up to beat the red light",
      "B": "B. Apply the brakes sharply to stop",
      "C": "C. Be prepared to stop in the center of the intersection",
      "D": "D. Be prepared to stop before the intersection"
    },
    {
      "id": "C4Q3",
      "answer": "B",
      "question": "Which of the following must you obey over the other three?",
      "A": "A. A steady red light",
      "B": "B. A policeman",
      "C": "C. A stop sign",
      "D": "D. A flashing red light"
    },
    {
      "id": "C4Q4",
      "answer": "B",
      "question": "You may cross a double solid yellow line:",
      "A": "A. To pass a slow moving truck",
      "B": "B. To turn into a driveway",
      "C": "C. To pass a car if traffic permits",
      "D": "D. Under no conditions"
    },
    {
      "id": "C4Q5",
      "answer": "A",
      "question": "You may not cross a single broken white (or yellow) line:",
      "A": "A. When to do so would interfere with traffic",
      "B": "B. When turning left into a driveway",
      "C": "C. When the car in front is disabled",
      "D": "D. When passing to the right on a one-way street"
    },
    {
      "id": "C4Q6",
      "answer": "D",
      "question": "What are the colors of a sign which tells you the distance to the next exit of a highway?",
      "A": "A. Yellow with black letters",
      "B": "B. Black with white letters",
      "C": "C. Red with white letters",
      "D": "D. Green with white letters"
    },
    {
      "id": "C4Q7",
      "answer": "B",
      "question": "A traffic light which has a green arrow and a red light means that:",
      "A": "A. You may only drive straight ahead",
      "B": "B. You may drive only in the direction of the green arrow",
      "C": "C. You must wait for a green light",
      "D": "D. Vehicles moving in any direction must stop"
    },
    {
      "id": "C4Q8",
      "answer": "B",
      "question": "What are the colors of the warning signs that indicate hazards ahead, such as curves in the road or narrow bridges?",
      "A": "A. Black letters or symbols on a white background",
      "B": "B. Black letters or symbols on a yellow background",
      "C": "C. White letters or symbols on a blue background",
      "D": "D. White letters or symbols on a green background"
    },
    {
      "id": "C4Q9",
      "answer": "A",
      "question": "You come to an intersection which has a flashing red light.  You should:",
      "A": "A. Come to a full stop, then go when safe to do so",
      "B": "B. Stop only if cars are approaching the intersection",
      "C": "C. Stop only if cars are already in the intersection",
      "D": "D. Slow down and be prepared to stop if necessary"
    },
    {
      "id": "C4Q10",
      "answer": "A",
      "question": "An intersection has a stop sign and a crosswalk, but no stop line.  You must stop:",
      "A": "A. Before the crosswalk",
      "B": "B. 50 feet before the intersection",
      "C": "C. Where you think the stop line would be",
      "D": "D. With your front wheels in the crosswalk"
    },
    {
      "id": "C4Q11",
      "answer": "C",
      "question": "When the road is marked with a solid yellow line and a broken yellow line on your side you may pass:",
      "A": "A. Only in an emergency",
      "B": "B. If you are on an expressway",
      "C": "C. If traffic is clear",
      "D": "D. Only at an intersection"
    },
    {
      "id": "C4Q12",
      "answer": "C",
      "question": "A rectangular-shaped sign is a:",
      "A": "A. Railroad crossing sign",
      "B": "B. School crossing sign",
      "C": "C. Speed limit sign",
      "D": "D. Stop sign"
    },
    {
      "id": "C4Q13",
      "answer": "B",
      "question": "What does a flashing yellow light mean?",
      "A": "A. Merging traffic",
      "B": "B. Proceed with caution",
      "C": "C. Pedestrian crossing",
      "D": "D. Come to a full stop"
    },
    {
      "id": "C4Q14",
      "answer": "B",
      "question": "What does this road sign mean?",
      "A": "A. Slow down and prepare to stop only if cars are approaching you",
      "B": "B. Come to a full stop, then go when it is safe to do so",
      "C": "C. Proceed carefully through the intersection, not always stopping",
      "D": "D. Stop only for traffic on an intersecting road"
    },
    {
      "id": "C4Q15",
      "answer": "A",
      "question": "A diamond-shaped sign is a:",
      "A": "A. Road hazard sign",
      "B": "B. Interstate route site",
      "C": "C. School crossing sign",
      "D": "D. Speed limit sign"
    },
    {
      "id": "C4Q16",
      "answer": "D",
      "question": "A solid white line on the right edge of the highway slants in toward your left.  This shows that:",
      "A": "A. There is an intersection just ahead",
      "B": "B. You are approaching a construction area",
      "C": "C. You will be required to turn left just ahead",
      "D": "D. The road will get narrower"
    },
    {
      "id": "C4Q17",
      "answer": "B",
      "question": "A red and white triangular sign at an intersection means:",
      "A": "A. Always come to a full stop at the intersection",
      "B": "B. Slow down and be prepared to stop if necessary",
      "C": "C. Slow down if an emergency vehicle is approaching",
      "D": "D. Look both ways as you cross the intersection"
    },
    {
      "id": "C4Q18",
      "answer": "D",
      "question": "Which of the following is used on some highways to direct drivers into the proper lanes for turning?",
      "A": "A. Flashing red lights",
      "B": "B. Flashing yellow lights",
      "C": "C. White lines on the side of the road",
      "D": "D. White arrows in the middle of the lanes"
    }
  ]
}